http://www.browniepointsinc.com/privacy-policy/

Menu
Search
Cart
Best SellersGift Types
Boozy GiftsBrownie GiftsBrownies, Popcorn & Confection GiftsGift Baskets & TowersGluten Free GiftsShop Local
Featured Flavors
Baby BrowniesBoozy BrowniesGluten Free BrowniesPopcorn FlavorsGourmet Brownie Bites
Occasions
Holiday Gift Boxes and BasketsCollege Care PackagesCongratulations!Fabulous FavorsGet Well / SympathyHappy Birthday!New BabySport GiftsThank You
By Price
Under $25$26 - $50$51 - $75$76 and Up
Business GiftsBusiness Gifts
Holiday Discount ProgramBusiness Gift SelectionsCustom Logo RibbonCorporate Form UploadChristmas Business Gifts
Multiple Addresses
Instructions1 - Login / Create account2 - Add addresses after loginBulk Order Form (Quantity over 16)
Sign up for our mailing list and receive 10% off your first order
Best SellersGift Types
Boozy GiftsBrownie GiftsBrownies, Popcorn & Confection GiftsGift Baskets & TowersGluten Free GiftsShop Local
Featured Flavors
Baby BrowniesBoozy BrowniesGluten Free BrowniesPopcorn FlavorsGourmet Brownie Bites
Occasions
Holiday Gift Boxes and BasketsCollege Care PackagesCongratulations!Fabulous FavorsGet Well / SympathyHappy Birthday!New BabySport GiftsThank You
By Price
Under $25$26 - $50$51 - $75$76 and Up
Business Gifts
Holiday Discount ProgramBusiness Gift SelectionsCustom Logo RibbonCorporate Form UploadChristmas Business Gifts
Multiple Addresses
Instructions1 - Login / Create account2 - Add addresses after loginBulk Order Form (Quantity over 16)
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?We
collect information from you when you register on the site, place an
order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or
communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.When
ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address,
mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other
information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.We
also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill
the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is
not used for marketing purposes.Like many websites, we use
"cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about
visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use
'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use
them.How do we use your information?We
may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase
products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or
marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site
features in the following ways:To personalize your site
experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product
offerings in which you are most interested.To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.To quickly process your transactions.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.If
you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you
periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional
e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or
modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have
not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these
e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features
such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a
choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive
e-mail communications from us.How do we protect visitor information?We
implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your
personal information. Your personal information is contained behind
secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons
who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep
the information confidential. When you place orders or access your
personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All
sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket
Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only
accessed as stated above.Do we use "cookies"?Yes.
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers
to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)
that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your
browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we
use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping
cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on
previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with
improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate
data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better
site experiences and tools in the future.We may contract with
third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our
site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the
information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and
improve our business.You can choose to have your computer warn
you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all
cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or
Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look
at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your
cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features
that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services
will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the
telephone by contacting customer service.Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?We
do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance
notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not
include www.browniepointsinc.com. It also does not include website
hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our
website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those
parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release
your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with
the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights,
property, or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor
information may be provided to other parties for marketing,
advertising, or other uses.How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?To
modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your
preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email
production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.To
delete all of your online account information from our database, sign
into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping
addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that
we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in
order to service that transaction and for record keeping.Third party linksIn
an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third
party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and
independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or
liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.
Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome
any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does
not work).Changes to our policyIf
we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on
this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after
the date of the change. This policy was last modified on August 6, 2003.Questions and feedbackWe
welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please
send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.Online Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.Your consentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
QUICK LINKSAbout UsPrivacy PolicyShipping InformationTerms and ConditionsBrownie VideosKosher InformationBuy Brownies OnlineNutritional InformationContact Us
ACCOUNT LINKSCreate AccountOrders and Returns
CONTACT USCALL: 800-427-9643EMAIL: info@browniepointsinc.comColumbus Store M-F  9:00 am to 4:00 pm
CONNECT WITH US
